tiptopmovie.com 2013-05-19

# Privacy Policy from tiptopmovie.com

###   
TipTopMovie.com Privacy Policy

Wow, you are interested… We hope the following information can help answer any questions you might have. And if you still want to know more, please drop us a line by clicking 

.

The following Privacy Statement discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for TipTopMovie.com Network of Web sites (which we collectively refer to below as the “Site”). 

Our Site, like most other sites, uses cookies to provide you with a more personalized and user-friendly experience. A cookie is a message that is sent to a browser from a Web server and stored on your computer’s hard drive. Cookies help us keep track of the size of our audience, the frequency of visits to our Site and the areas that are most popular. If a guest makes a purchase, cookies are used to keep the shopping cart active during the shopping process. We may also use cookies to help us deliver content or advertising specific to your interests, and to save your preferences or passwords so you don't have to re-enter them each time you visit our Site. Most browsers allow you to reject all cookies, but then your preferences, passwords and other information will not be saved, and you may have to re-enter information to use certain features of our Site. 

We may use an outside ad company to display ads on our Site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies delivered through banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information. TipTopMovie.com may also serve banner ads that contain cookies. We will only share such information with our advertisers and sponsors on an aggregate basis to determine the success of any given banner, logo or advertisement. 

  The Site contains links and advertisements to other sites. If you click-through a banner ad or link and submit your information to that advertiser or site, you will be subject to their own privacy practices. TipTopMovie.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other sites. 

The Site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and that if you disclose personal contact information in these areas, others may use it to send you unsolicited messages. We do not control the actions of our guests and members. TipTopMovie.com encourages our users to be smart about choosing when, and to whom to release information online.

Of course there are many other ways we conceivably could get information from or about you that are not described elsewhere in this Statement. For example, you might email us through one of our customer service email addresses, or we may get a complaint about you from a third party. Our practices with respect to such information are pretty much as you’d expect -- we use and disclose this information in a commercially reasonable business manner. 

This site has industry consistent security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. But since the Internet cannot be made absolutely secure, TipTopMovie.com assumes no liability for disclosure of data due to errors in transmission or unauthorized third parties. 

If you are a minor under 12, you are prohibited from submitting any personal information to us. 

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving promotional/marketing information from TipTopMovie.com and our partners. We also provide instructions for how to unsubscribe to future mailings at the bottom of each communication. Please remember to check the registration screens applicable to the service or promotion for which you are signing up for specific instructions from our partners on how to update your user profile and/or opt out of receiving offers and mailings.

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact: [info@tiptopmovie.com](mailto:info@tiptopmovie.com)

  By using the Site, you signify your acceptance of this Privacy Statement. If you are not comfortable with any policy described in this Privacy Statement, you may feel free to e-mail us with questions or concerns, but your only remedy is to discontinue use of the Site. We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Statement at any time. 

###  Third Party Advertising

We use Guruji and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please click **here**. 

###  Third Party Cookies

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique “cookie” on your browser.
